<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[KP Law Firm (Grid-manual)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[KP Law Firm (Grid-manual)]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 07:22:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Constantinos Klissouras]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Constantinos Klissouras</h1><p>Constantinos Klissouras heads the firm’s disputes and restructuring team, specializing in complex civil and commercial litigation and arbitration, finance, and domestic and cross-border restructuring and insolvency.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/constantinos-klissouras/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2bd0a12f-c0bd-467d-b695-9a345a502820</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 07:20:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Christina Papachristopoulou]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Christina Papachristopoulou</h1><p>Christina Papachristopoulou is a finance, corporate & commercial, and capital markets partner, specializing in the entire spectrum of finance transactions, structures and methodologies and complex corporate transactions. She has a wide record in corporate law matters, group/corporate structuring and restructuring, including cross-border mergers, spin offs, stakeholder agreements, debt and equity financing, export financing, has advised Greek corporates in their listing on the AIM of the LSE and qualified investors in their participation in AIFs. She has been involved in some of the most significant privatisations in Greece over the past decade, involving various methodologies (IPOs, secondary offerings, accelerated book building and other OTC transactions). She is a recognised expert in sovereign finance and has advised syndicate lenders and portfolio managers on GGB issues, sovereign default and restructuring. She has co-authored in English on cash-pooling (GLB, 2012) and the HR Privatisation Programme (LFMR, 2012). </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/christina-papachristopoulou/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0e817129-91fc-4b12-8c4a-9fd64fecefea</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 07:15:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domna Kyrzopoulou]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Domna Kyrzopoulou</h1><p>Domna Kyrzopoulou is a corporate and commercial law partner and heads the firm’s competition, antitrust and intellectual property rights disputes and transactions practice. She has an established record in intellectual property and unfair competition disputes and considerable experience in representing legal entities before the Hellenic Competition Commission. Early in her career (2003), she obtained in front of the Plenary Session of the Hellenic Competition Commission one of the most durable cases, ruling on AEPI (the Greek collecting society) abusing its dominant position. She has represented the biggest software, advertising, broadcasting and production companies. Widely experienced in all types of commercial law transactions as well as diverse corporate restructuring procedures, she has systematically developed proprietary contractual and licensing models and has advised multinational corporations on anti-counterfeit strategies enforcement.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/domna-kyrzopoulou/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f600c18a-1d44-44ff-86ce-be2b80a1b861</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 07:12:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dionysios Gavounelis]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Dionysios Gavounelis</h1><p>Dionysis Gavounelis is a dispute resolution partner, and heads the firm’s procurement & construction team, specialising in complex litigation, and the full spectrum of procurement, through tendering, contracting, execution and the resolution of disputes.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/dionysios-gavounelis/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5470320f-7709-4906-ac4b-d7911ae4acb4</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 07:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sovereign Finance]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sovereign Finance</h1><p>We are at the forefront of the law and practice related to the sovereign debt crisis. Partners at KP have established  track records advising managers of general syndicated and special sovereign issues, as well as  large portfolio managers on secondary market transactions.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/sovereign-finance/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">74622eda-32af-4f55-a47b-ae998887db4d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:35:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Privatization]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Privatization</h1><p>Partners at KP have had leading roles in some of the most significant privatizations of the previous 1990s and 2000s privatizations waves. We have seen through the partial privatization of electricity, telecoms and other industries, from inception to implementation, to post transaction conduct of disputes and settlement of claims, acting principally for financial advisers, but occasionally also for the HR.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/privatization/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d0d51bd8-4235-428b-82aa-711297baacf8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Media & Entertainment]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Media & Entertainment</h1><p>In an increasingly complex regulatory environment governing distribution models and technologies, across multiple platforms and international borders, it makes a difference to engage a well-resourced team that pieces together the high theory and hands-on practice of media, media transactions and related disputes, equipped with strong insights in intellectual property, antitrust and competition law, and groomed to work up from solid finance and disputes foundations.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/media-and-entertainment/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc7d384-1444-4001-815f-711a12f67a70</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infrastructure]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Infrastructure</h1><p>At KP we have advised and represented engineering and construction firms and JVs in major road, railway and subway projects and have successfully conducted large value, multi-party and cross-border disputes arising from complex EPC hot and cold industrial, electromechanical and civil works in transportation and heavy industry projects.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/infrastructure/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">08c2bf49-f4a5-4c6d-830d-ac59bbb93efd</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:32:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare & Life Sciences]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Healthcare & Life Sciences</h1><p>We regularly act for manufacturers, distributors and service providers of medical equipment, single use medical devices, prescription and non-prescription medicines and pharmaceutical substances in regulatory, compliance,  transactional and contentious matters.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/healthcare-and-life-sciences/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1a8e7a23-e284-4c62-8fcd-7299bee034b3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:31:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Financial Services]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Financial Services</h1><p>The partners at KP have established track records acting for most types of credit and financial institutions; we have acted for many of the larger global and international investment banks, securities houses, investment, hedge and private equity funds, trustees, custodians and underwriters, insurers and reinsurers, and their directors and officers.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/kp-law-firm-grid-manual/financial-services/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1730bc7f-1db0-479c-8a69-3a1ce81a989a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:30:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>